<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SUV on Toyota</title><link>/en/tags/suv/</link><description>Recent content in SUV on Toyota</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/en/tags/suv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>COROLLA CROSS</title><link>/en/blog/1/01/01/corolla-cross/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/blog/1/01/01/corolla-cross/</guid><description>COROLLA CROSS REINVENT THE RULES
Crossover from RM 130,400.00
All Corolla Cross Models: Corolla Cross Hybrid Electric From RM142,000.00.00
Engine: 1.8 L, 4-cyl Petrol Toyota Safety Sense Kick-sensor Power Back Door Corolla Cross 1.8V AT From RM137,400.00
Engine: 1.8 L, 4-cyl Petrol Toyota Safety Sense Kick-sensor Power Back Door Corolla Cross 1.8G AT From RM130,400.00
Engine: 1.8 L, 4-cyl Petrol Kick-sensor Power Back Door Corolla Cross GR Sport From RM142,000.00</description></item><item><title>FORTUNER</title><link>/en/blog/1/01/01/fortuner/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/blog/1/01/01/fortuner/</guid><description>FORTUNER PURE DUALITY
SUV from RM 189,880.00
All Fortuner Models: Fortuner 2.8 VRZ AT 4WD From RM230,880.00
Engine: 2.8 L Turbo Diesel Torque: 500 Nm Auto Limited-slip Differential (LSD) Fortuner 2.7 SRZ AT 4WD From RM191,880.00
Engine: 2.7 L Petrol Torque: 245 Nm Auto Limited-slip Differential (LSD) Fortuner 2.4 AT 4WD From RM189,880.00
Engine: 2.4 L Diesel Torque: 400 Nm On-the-road price including SST, without insurance for models in Peninsular Malaysia (for Individual Private Owners).</description></item><item><title>HARRIER</title><link>/en/blog/1/01/01/harrier/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/blog/1/01/01/harrier/</guid><description>HARRIER FEEL THE PRESENCE
Sedan from RM 274,000.00
All Harrier Models: Harrier 2.0 Luxury SE From RM277,000.00
Direct Shift-CVT 40% Thermal Efficiency TNGA Platform With Trailing DWB Rear Suspension Harrier 2.0 Luxury From RM274,000.00
Direct Shift-CVT 40% Thermal Efficiency TNGA Platform With Trailing DWB Rear Suspension On-the-road price including SST, without insurance for models in Peninsular Malaysia (for Individual Private Owners). Prices shown are subject to change and are governed by the terms and conditions of this website.</description></item><item><title>RUSH</title><link>/en/blog/1/01/01/rush/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/blog/1/01/01/rush/</guid><description>RUSH ABOVE. AHEAD. ALWAYS.
SUV from RM 93,000.00
All Rush Models: Rush 1.5S AT From RM97,000.00
Pre-Collision System (PCS) Blind Spot Monitor with Rear Cross Traffic Alert (RCTA) Panoramic View Monitor (PVM) Rush 1.5G AT From RM93,000.00
Blind Spot Monitor with Rear Cross Traffic Alert (RCTA) Panoramic View Monitor (PVM) On-the-road price including SST, without insurance for models in Peninsular Malaysia (for Individual Private Owners). Prices shown are subject to change and are governed by the terms and conditions of this website.</description></item></channel></rss>